This claim angered another Russian mathematician,
هذا يدعون angered اخر عالم رياضيات الروسية
Andrey Markov, who maintained a very public
andrey markov , الذين الحفاظ على العامة جدا
animosity towards Nekrasov.
العداء نحو nekrasov .
He goes on to say in a letter that "this circumstance
على ان اقوله في رسالة هذه الظروف التي &quot;
"prompts me to explain in a series of articles
&quot; ان اشرح prompts في سلسلة من المقالات
"that the law of large numbers can apply
&quot; ان اعداد كبيرة من يمكن تطبيق القانون
"to dependent variables,"
تعتمد المتغيرات , &quot; الى &quot;
using a construction which he brags
brags البناء باستخدامه
Nekrasov cannot even dream about.
لا يمكنك حتى عن nekrasov حلم .
Markov extends Bernoulli's results
نتائج برنولي markov تمتد
to dependent variables using an ingenious construction.
تعتمد المتغيرات لاستخدام بارع للبناء .
Imagine a coin flip which isn't independent,
تخيلوا العملة المعدنية وليس مستقلة ,
but dependent on the previous outcome,
ولكن , تعتمد على نتائج السابقة
so it has short-term memory of one event.
لذا فقد من الذاكرة قصيرة المدى .
This can be visualized using a hypothetical
هذا يمكن ان تظهر باستخدام افتراضي
machine which contains two cups,
اثنين , الذي يحتوي على الة الاكواب
which we call states.
والذي نسميه .
In one state we have a 50-50 mix
في ولاية واحدة لدينا خلط 50-50
of light versus dark beads,
من الضوء والظلام الخرز ,
while in the other state we have more dark versus light.
بينما نحن في حالة اخرى لدينا المزيد من الضوء والظلام .
One cup we can call state zero.
يمكننا ان نسميه كاس واحد حالة الصفر .
It represents a dark having previously occurred,
انها تمثل مظلم وحدث , سابقا
and the other state, we can call one,
والاخرى , يمكننا ان ندعو واحد ,
it represents a light bead having previously occurred.
انها تمثل خرزة ضوء حصل على سابقا .
To run our machine, we simply start in a random state
الة لنا , نحن ببساطة في حالة بعشوائية
and make a selection.
وجعل الاختيار .
Then we move to either state zero or one,
ومن ثم ننتقل الى ولاية واحدة , او اما صفر
depending on that event.
اعتمادا على هذا الحدث .
Based on the outcome of that selection,
انه يعتمد على نتيجة الانتقاء
we output either a zero if it's dark,
اما اذا اخراجنا في الظلام , انها صفر
or a one if it's light.
او اذا كان احد الضوء .
With this two-state machine,
مع هذه الالة , الدولة
we can identify four possible transitions.
يمكننا تحديد اربعة ممكن تنتقل .
If we are in state zero and a black occurs,
اذا نحن في حالة الصفر ويحدث ,
we loop back to the same state and select again.
نحن حلقة العودة الى نفس واختيار مرة اخرى .
If a light bead is selected, we jump over
اذا , نحن الضوء هو اختيار خرزة القفز فوق
to state one, which can also loop back on itself,
واحد , والتي يمكن ان الدولة ايضا , حلقة العودة على نفسها
or jump back to state zero if a dark is chosen.
او القفز الى الدولة اذا هو اختيار مظلم صفر .
The probability of a light versus dark selection
احتمال ضوء مقابل الانتقاء المظلمة
is clearly not independent here,
هنا , هو انه لا مستقلة
since it depends on the previous outcome.
بما انه يعتمد على نتائج السابق .
But Markov proved that as long as every state
لكن markov اثبات ذلك طالما كل ولاية
in the machine is reachable, when you run
في هذه الالة , عندما تدير reachable
these machines in a sequence,
هذه الالات , في سلسلة
they reach equilibrium.
تصل التوازن .
That is, no matter where you start,
هذا هو , لا يهم اين تبدا ,
once you begin the sequence,
حالما تبدا التسلسل ,
the number of times you visit each state
عدد مرات الزيارة كل دولتك
converges to some specific ratio, or a probability.
لبعض converges محددة النسبة , او الاحتمالات .
This simple example disproved Nekrasov's claim
هذا المثال البسيط يدعون nekrasov disprovedه
that only independent events could converge
ان مستقلة يمكن ان تتقارب الاحداث
on predictable distributions.
في توزيعات يمكن التنبؤ بها .